http://www.bowvalleycollege.ca/about/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Bow Valley College is committed to ensuring the personal privacy of learners, faculty, staff and customers visiting our website.
Commitment
Bow Valley College is committed to providing our visitors with a website that respects their privacy. This page summarizes the privacy policy and practices on the Bow Valley College website.
Links to Other Websites
This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read the privacy policy of each site that you visit before proceeding further.
Cookies
We use cookies and location services to improve your experience on our site and to send you personalised advertising.
Some websites store information in a small text file, called a "cookie," on your hard disk. Cookies contain information about you and your preferences (e.g., a record of which pages within the site you visited) to help the site customize the view for you the next time you visit. Only the information that you provide, or the choices you make while visiting a website, can be stored in a cookie. For example, the site cannot determine your e-mail name unless you choose to provide it.
Allowing a website to create a cookie does not give that or any other site access to the rest of your computer, and only the site that created the cookie can read it.
Cookies can be enabled/disabled by selecting Tools -> Internet Options. Select the Security tab and then select Custom Level. The cookie settings will be displayed in the Security Settings dialog box.
Personal Information Collected Through This Website
We do not automatically gather any personal information from you, such as your name, phone number, e-mail, or address. If you send us e-mail or use our feedback form to contact us, you will be providing us with some personal information including your name, e-mail and perhaps information about your personal circumstances. This information is only used to process and respond to your question or comment, and is collected in compliance with the Alberta Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (the FOIP Act). This information is not disclosed except to authorized personnel who need it to answer your question.
Bow Valley College is subject to the Alberta government's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.
Contact Us
FOIP coordinator
Debbie Hayman
403-410-1445
dhayman@bowvalleycollege.ca
Please note: Due to current Canada Post delays, please send all FOIP requests via email.
If you are currently studying in a post-secondary program at BVC, please register for your courses via mybvc to ensure your enrolments and fees are processed appropriately.
Cart total based on domestic tuition rates. For information about International Tuition rates please see
Fee Information
If you anticipate applying for a student loan, your payment will be refunded to you based on your loan award once your funding has been received by BVC.
Your cart is currently empty.
Why Bow Valley College?
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. Learn more in our privacy policy
I accept
